<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My Website</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Blog Post no. 1</title>
      <link>/post/2020/12/11/test-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020/12/11/test-post/</guid>
      <description>Python and R! After taking this course, I have gained more knowledge about R Studio and began learning about Python! I have learned their differences, but they can still give the same outputs and can intertwine/communicate with one another using reticulate.
Working With Reticulate First, I had to install reticulate from its library. Here is the R Studio code in assigning content to a variable:
library(reticulate) school &amp;lt;- &amp;quot;One More&amp;quot; Here is the Python code in assigning content to a variable:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Modeling, Testing, and Predicting</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>Introduction My dataset includes numerical, categorical, and binary variables about police-reported car accidents that resulted in a harmful event and at least one car was towed in the year 1999. I found this interesting because people can be reckless drivers and I wanted to see the information on these accidents because I was also born in 1999. Thisdata is pertaining to the front seat occupant at the time of the accident.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The two datasets I have chosen were the happiness scale numbers of countries and the alcohol consumption that corresponds to those countries to see if there is a correlation between the two. The variables within this are the country, the happines ranking, the happiness score, and the alcohol consumption per capita. The alcohol consumption per capita is divided in three sections: beer, spirits, and wine. I picked this because I knew about the happiest countries and also how alcohol is a depressant, so I am wondering how their alcohol consumption will impact their emotions causing a decrease or increase in happiness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description> Check out some of my coding projects below:
 Wrangling &amp;amp; Exploratory Data Analysis
 Modeling, Inference, Prediction
  -- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
